The Neighbors Club Activity Report for today shows training camp at the beach.
This ought to be interesting.
Finally, I can sit down.
Me too!
I think I'll sit here with you guys.
Just pick one.
Where's Rika? Have you seen her?
Last I heard, she was looking around the train for the coupling section.
What the heck is that?
No! How'd I get the old maid again?
C-c-c-that was a prelude.
Someday soon I'll be playing your final requiem. Be prepared.
This one.
Oh, I got the old maid.
That's what you get for being a poopy vampire.
Pardon me while I win this game.
Hmm. Gimme.
Ah! It's the stupid old maid!
You're lying!
That's what you школed.
it's really gonna take us an hour to walk from the station there's not even a bus or a cab we
can call that's because most normal people just take their own car from the train station well
we're not getting anywhere by standing here you coming yeah what else are we gonna do
oh yeah normally in this kind of situation the faculty advisor would be the one driving us you
know that right don't be ridiculous even if I am a genius there's no way I could get a driver's
license I couldn't reach the pedal thanks for bringing actually hanging in there I kind of
thought you'd be the first one down Rika had her batteries recharged in the coupling section
there was something about the way those strong pieces of iron fit so tightly together they'd
thrust in and out of each other with every movement of the train it was a loud rough erotic
rhythm all that banging underneath Rika made her feel like getting off and doing the nasty
yes it's the ocean ocean ocean you finally made it wait the beach house is this way
this place is amazing are you sure it's okay for us to train here I'm positive I don't want to
train I want to swim I'm gonna go swimming okay sometimes it's so obvious what a baby you are we can
swim after we unpack
okay we're at the ocean we have to do that thing what's
where we all look out to sea strike a hot pose and then we yell yeah see it's what we call
humiliation play I don't even want to know what that's all about I've heard of it before I think
one of the characters in the video game I was playing was pretty into it yeah I think I've seen
this too and got really creeped out what does it mean exactly is it some ritual for the gleeful
maybe that's it maybe we're just not happy enough to understand I don't think that's the case but we
should probably practice that's a good idea what if we come back here with other friends and they
don't know how to do a pose we would need to know how to show them wouldn't we is being happier really
something you can practice what do we do again stare at the ocean and yell at it what would be the
point of that let's give it a try when I give you the signal shout as loud as you can pick any pose you
want ready I'll go first one two it does not like choking on salt air was that supposed to make me feel
happier yeah didn't it yeah I guess so I think this is the kind of thing we should all practice
separately let's put off yelling at the ocean as a group until we can do it on our own okay how do we
know if we're good at it I'm being summoned by the color blue ocean waves and skies are calling to
me coba toe get over here and put some sunblock on you know better your council makes me weary I
must shield my skin from sun so the water won't hurt me you're gonna be all right no it doesn't you
need to put some on too I never carry any of that stuff with me but I think I'll be fine I need
some cover this body and UV barrier cream uh yeah you look like you'd burn pretty easily brother would
you wrap lotion all over me too please of course you're next right after Maria I'm grateful and
I'd like to repay your kindness I can't take this so many naked body parts touching each other it's too hot
even though Yuki's nervous his heartbeats in anticipation without even thinking about it he puts
you know what inside Kodakus you know what gently a person that it's so big bigger than expected
whatever that's supposed to mean
yeah in case you're wondering I do need help putting lotion on my back what you know there's
nothing you can do to protect processed meat from going bad don't you quit treating me like a
disease you're so right I'd love to help you here goes butch up prom queen your hands are like
freakishly huge and you can use less lotion you know it'll feel better once you're used to it what
please that's what you think I'm used to morons on my back right just relax
um why does it feel like you have monkey hands you're imagining things I wish you could feel this
I swear I'm being groped by a mutant what the hell do you think you're doing that's disgusting I
wouldn't try to get up if I were you why what are you doing to me I'm pressing on your center of
gravity no matter how hard you try you won't be able to move it's amusing actually let's discuss
how stupid it was for you to trust me with something like this I don't care just get your
feet off of me you've got the lotion on your back what difference does it make if I use my feet makes
a huge difference no one steps on me I'm the one who walks all over me trust me I know that's true
and there's nothing I enjoy more than seeing you get back a little of what you've been giving out
here you go does that feel better you're welcome no that doesn't feel better and it's highly
inappropriate you don't get to step on a goddess's back I'm the one who does the stepping what's kind
of weird is I think you actually enjoy having me on your back like this meat look at your body's
quivering shut up it's not true stop I don't believe you you don't want me to stop you like
feeling helpless you need to be told what to do totally humiliated and forced to perform
exclusively for my entertainment we have words for people like you brubella people who get pleasure
out of stuff like this you're such a pervert now you're my slave I'm not a pervert it doesn't feel
good I hate this oh just admit it you love being told what to do don't you you little bitch this is
exactly who you are tell everyone you're a pervert look at you covered in crap you want this you crave
it tell me tell me you want me to walk all over you beg for it it's time to obey your goddess you
filthy slave you're crazy now don't you ever say those things about me again I am not a pervert I am
a goddess and a princess do you understand me that's hilarious you're funny when you get brave
I thought for some reason she'd be a little more relaxed at the beach
here we go
am I the only one who knows how to cook around here where's the yogurt
hey what are you doing out here you okay oh hi Kodika so earlier today did you you know
see anything huh what do you mean when I stood up before I left oh no I was too busy putting sunblock
on Kobito and listening to her freak out is this because of yosara is she teasing you again
yeah you know how she can be forget about it I just made dinner for us
hey wait up this feels amazing let's go that way
I'll take two of these please
what are you making it smells kind of weird paella tonight I bought everything on the other side of
town so it's much cheaper I'm amazed you even know how to make that yeah it's one of Kobito's favorite
dishes so what about you what kind of things do you make you took a cooking class didn't you
yeah but it doesn't really matter all I did in that class was stand alone in the corner and wait to leave
everyone would ignore me the instructor taught the classes if I wasn't even there
after they finished making their meal they put a little on my plate it was like they were feeding a dog or a homeless girl
I'd eat it anyway because I was hungry but it was humiliating
I'd always be the first one to finish eating and then I would get stuck washing everyone else's dishes
so that's all I ever learned in cooking class
wow that's terrible
I'm impressed Kodika this is good
Mika thinks it's delicious
I must say you've outdone yourself this time sir
it was so sweet of him to make this
shut up you stupid vampire what the heck did I do to you
looks like tonight's the last of our training camp now that we're going home I'm realizing we never did
any of the things you're supposed to do on these trips is there an activity list or something if you
practice looking at the ocean and yelling at it what more do you want from us and how does that count as
normal for what it's worth Rika would like to do more before we go like what like when a girl is
cold and she crawls into a boy's sleeping bag dude quit being such a weird pervert hurt then how about
something more predictable like telling ghost stories or playing truth or dare I'm surprised a
science chick would even be into games or telling ghost stories we all love stories about the
supernatural it's fascinating Rika may be a scientist but she's also just a girl with a pure heart and a
dirty mind yeah we've noticed that someone did a dare in twinkle school today I kind of want to try it huh
so let's start by sharing scary stories then after we're totally freaked out we can go into the forest and
see who can last the longest I like that idea I like whatever big bro likes nothing is more comforting to me
than the darkness I will be protected and I'm not frightened I'm not scared of ghosts or haunted forests let's do this
okay we'll start with Rika since it was her idea Rika feels guilty about how high she's gonna set this bar
one night there was a big black book with the words ultra mecca written on the cover but inside the book
it said ultra magical and then what happened huh nothing that's the end great who's next I believe
I'm ready to go scary steamed meat that sounds like a funny story no it's not it's actually very scary
who's next I hope you're all wearing thick underwear because I'm about to drag you into a pit of terror you've
never even imagined that was an amazing buildup why aren't you scared who's next I'll go I've been
sitting on this for a while but I think you guys can handle it the name of it is the miso soup night of
terror I don't get why it's so funny it's not that's the story you keep in your back pocket do you not
know what scary is that's weird I could ask you guys the same thing since you all suck at making
things up I'll tell a true story then we can move on a friend of mine told me about this in
confidence a long time ago you don't have any friends this is fake just shut your face to protect
her privacy I'm going to call her echo this is something that's been haunting me for years when
echo was in middle school she only had one really close friend they were inseparable and did everything
together we'll call that friend why go for now in their hearts they were sisters and only had each
other their school was known all over town for being haunted everyone who went there had a story
about the ghost called Yamako a past student who died on campus however they say she only haunts those
who've betrayed their close friends students who are loyal have never seen her anyone who ever does
though dies both girls liked the same guy to protect their friendship they promised each other they
would not pursue him one day echo broke her promise it drove white go to commit suicide after that incident
echo started noticing all kinds of strange things happening around her it got worse and worse until one day
after that night echo just disappeared and was never heard from again
okay is everyone ready to go out into the forest we're all really tired I think we should call it a
night plus it's dark outside we might trip or something something happened we'd be lost no one would ever
find us it's okay guys we don't have to do the bravery test
yozara's story really freaked me out but I started to realize it wasn't the part about the ghost that kept
me up honestly it was the whole broken promises leading to suicide thing I thought about my best
friend from when I was a kid and what he did it made me wonder if he thinks I'm the one who hurt him
you gotta be kidding
hi Kodaka you awake
Senna what are you doing in here will you come with me I need a favor
okay where are we going I have to go to the bathroom and the halls are dark
what on earth and it's not because I'm scared okay I'm totally fine I just need someone there in case
you know in case I need someone there why didn't you ask yozara to help you you guys are sharing a
room are you crazy she'd just make fun if I asked her to help me with this so can we please hurry I'm
seriously about to be on the floor okay fine
you're still out there aren't you Kodaka yeah I'm still here
hey are you still out there Kodaka are you there I said I was well I didn't hear you stop yelling
are you still there I haven't moved
if you tell yozara this ever happened I'll completely deny it and I swear I'll never forgive
you okay let's go what's the matter will you please take me to the bathroom hello are you still out
there yep I'm right here bathroom right whoa that was an amazing trick you must be a psychic or
something yeah just hurry up I gotta sleep at some point
I'm almost done yes I'll take you to the bathroom hold on bathroom Rico's fine with the bed but that
sounds much more exciting go to sleep I should have gone while I was up the first three times
what's the matter are you okay why are you up because I have to pee hey that's funny so do I
and since we're both up why don't we go down there together don't tell me you're scared you're the
one who was telling the story why are you so freaked out no I'm not why would you say something that
ridiculous there's nothing to be ashamed of I just want to know how you scared yourself
because the goal was to scare people if I wasn't affected by it I couldn't guarantee they'd be
so um I have a question you can go in first it's cool thanks
hey Kodaka are you still out there I sure am
still there yep don't forget I still have to go so it would be really stupid of me to leave
right that makes sense
sorry about that all good
you don't have to ask I'll stay here and wait for you to finish
so seriously you weren't affected by my story at all nope not even a little bit I'm impressed
you're a lot braver than I thought look at that wow
but I really did like the moral about not betraying your friends yeah
so did I
When we were telling ghost stories,
I intentionally made my story a little lamer than yours.
What are you talking about?
Everyone knows I'm better at the funny stories,
so I step back and let you have your moment.
Ugh, good night.
What's with the cutoff? Fine, I won't tell a story then.
How about a stand-up routine?
I'll make you laugh till your sides hurt.
No, thank you.
At least hear the subjects.
No.
Oh, don't be a pooper.
Next, episode 11.
Girls are super cute and you caught us.
Okay, so a chicken walks into a bar and...
Where'd you go?
What's with the scar?
Okay.
Good night, everyone.
You're welcome.
Good night.
Good night, everyone.
It's all this we have from you.
Boop.
Good night.